Guide to the Outdoor Advertising Association of America (OAAA) Archives, 1885-2017 and undated RL.00963
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
SICMEA: Societe Industrielle du Constructions Metalliques En Acier (French billboard construction and posting company)
SMRB: Simmons Market Research Bureau (research company)
TAB: Traffic Audit Bureau (research company; a non-profit organization dedicated to producing authenticated circulation values for outdoor advertising markets)
USO: United Service Organizations (U.S. public service agency)
Advertising laws; Advertising, Outdoor -- Canada; Advertising, Outdoor -- England; Slides (photographs); Advertising, Outdoor -- Law and legislation -- United States; Outdoor Advertising Association of America -- Organization; Outdoor Advertising Association of America -- Membership; Outdoor Advertising Association of America -- Chairman's Advisory Committee; Advertising -- Automobiles -- United States -- Case studies; Outdoor Advertising Association of America -- Barney Link Fellowship Committee; Outdoor Advertising Association of America -- Buildings; Advertising, Outdoor -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Photographs; Billboards; Energy policy -- United States; Highway law -- United States; Traffic safety -- United States; World War, 1939-1945 -- United States -- Propaganda; Outdoor Advertising Association of America -- Research; Negatives (photographs); The Poster [serial]; Association of National Advertisers; Associated Bill Posters' Association; Cawl, Frank; Bruskin Associates; Coolidge, Calvin, 1872-1933; Columbus Outdoor; Ford Motor Company; Daniel Starch and Staff; A.C. Nielsen Company; Advertising Federation of America; Advertising Council; American Association of Advertising Agencies; American Advertising Federation; Associated Advertising Clubs of America; American Automobile Association; Wilson, Woodrow; Raymond Loewy Associates; Simmons Market Research Bureau; Poster Advertising Association; Outdoor Advertising, Inc.; Painted Outdoor Advertising Association; Outdoor Advertising Association of America; War Advertising Council; Wilbur Smith and Associates; United Advertising; University of Notre Dame; Tiffen Art Metal Company; Traffic Audit Bureau (New York, N.Y.); Swift & Company; Thomas Cusack Company; International Congress of Outdoor Advertising; International Bill Posters'Association of North America; Institute of Outdoor Advertising; Holan, Walter; Ghaster, Karl; General Outdoor Advertising Co; General Federation of Women's Clubs; R.C. Maxwell Co; Foster and Kleiser Company; New England Confectionery Company; National Safety Council; National Outdoor Advertising Bureau; Morton Salt Company; Lawton, Elizabeth; Kellogg Company; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; John Donnelly & Sons
- ADMINISTRATION-OFFICERS SERIES, 1935-1988 (bulk 1951-1974)
  Scope and Contents note
  The series includes biographical files on key OAAA officials; the personal files of several OAAA executives; as well as extensive files that have been identified as belonging to Frank Cawl, Karl Ghaster, and Walter Holan. These latter files contain personal correspondence, notes from committee meetings and planning sessions, as well as texts for speeches and presentations; they are of special interest to researchers interested in the wide range of activities undertaken by OAAA executives in the course of daily operations, and they provide a glimpse into the corporate culture of the OAAA at different times.
  Biographies are first, followed by materials arranged alphabetically by officer name or category. Letter size folders are followed by legal size folders in two runs.
  [NOTE: Some physically large materials have been removed to the Oversize Materials Series. A listing may be found at the end of this container list.]
  - Biographies of Various Officers (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    [See also Box AD20]
    - Fulton, Kerwin, 1948-1956 (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Hathaway, Odell, 1934-1960 (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Materials A-B, 1941-1962 (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Materials C-E, 1935-1952 and undated (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Materials F-H, 1927-1960 (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Materials I-L, undated (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Materials M-P, 1935-1954 (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Materials Q-R, 1952 and undated (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Materials S-V, 1941-1954 (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Materials W-Z, 1935 and undated (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Multiple Listings and Miscellaneous, 1956 and undated (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Paver, John, 1954-1960 (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Robbins, Burr L., 1953-1960 (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Standish, Myles, 1950-1958 (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Wilson, Harold, 1941-1950 (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Wrigley, Charles, 1939 (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
  - Cawl, Frank
    - AAAA Eastern Region Meeting, 1966 (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Advertising Age Media Buyers' Workshop, 1965-1967, 3 folders (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - Association of National Advertisers (ANA) Seminar, 1966, 2 folders (Box AD1 - Letter Size)
    - ANA Workshop, 1967 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - Area Meetings, 1966 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - Automotive Accounts, 1967 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - Baltimore, 1967 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - Berkeley Seminar, 1967 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - Biographies, 1973-1976 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - Boston Ad Club, 1966 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - Carling's- Cleveland, 1967 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - Convention Speeches, 1965 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - Des Moines Ad Club, 1967 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - D. P. Brother & Company, 1966-1967 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - Fact Book Material, 1965 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - Fiesta Gardens Roughs, 1966 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - Heublein (Gumbinner-North), 1967 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - Kentucky Outdoor Advertising Association, 1967 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - Marketing Agency Committee, 1966 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - Minneapolis Ad Club Presentation, 1966-1967 (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous Memos, 1975, 2 folders (Box AD2 - Letter Size)
    - National Competition, 1967 (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - Norwalk Community College, 1967 (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - Notre Dame, 1967 (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - Notre Dame Presentation, 1966, 2 folders (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - N. W. Ayer Presentation, 1966 (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - OAAA Canada- First Awards, 1966 (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - OAAA Michigan- Presentation, 1966 (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - OAAA Ohio- Convention Presentation, 1966 (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - Oklahoma City- National Outdoor, 1966 (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - Operation and Usage of the Medium of Outdoor Advertising, 1966 (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - Pittsburgh, 1967 (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - Presentation to Federal Governments Sub-Committees, 1967 (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - Purex Corporation Presentation, 1966 (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - Southwestern Association of Advertising Agencies Presentation, 1967 (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - St. Louis Ad Club Presentation, 1966 (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - Supermarket Presentations, 1966-1967, 2 folders (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - TAB Presentation, 1967 (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
    - U.S. Savings and Loan League, 1965 (Box AD3 - Letter Size)
  - Cawl, Frank- Committee Meetings (Box AD4 - Letter Size)
    - AAA Annual Meeting, 1973 (Box AD4 - Letter Size)
    - AAA Meeting, 1972 Nov. 3 (Box AD4 - Letter Size)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1972 Aug. 24 (Box AD4 - Letter Size)
    - Boca Raton Meeting, 1973 Feb. (Box AD4 - Letter Size)
    - Budget Meeting, 1972 Oct. 25 (Box AD4 - Letter Size)
    - COM Annual Meeting, 1972 (Box AD4 - Letter Size)
    - Committees' Acceptances, 1973 (Box AD4 - Letter Size)
    - Design Research Project [Orientation] Meeting, 1972 May (Box AD4 - Letter Size)
    - Design Research Project Meeting, 1972 Sept. (Box AD4 - Letter Size)
    - Environics Committee Meeting, 1972 Jan., 2 folders (Box AD4 - Letter Size)
    - Environics Meeting- Design Project, 1972 Nov. (Box AD4 - Letter Size)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1972 Jan. (Box AD4 - Letter Size)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1972 Mar. (Folder 1 of 2) (Box AD4 - Letter Size)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1972 Mar. (Folder 2 of 2) (Box AD5 - Letter Size)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1972 April, May, July-Sept., Dec.; 1973 Feb., May, 9 folders (Box AD5 - Letter Size)
    - Executive Committee Meeting, 1973 June, Aug., Sept., 3 folders (Box AD6 - Letter Size)
    - Financial Committee, 1973-1974 (Box AD6 - Letter Size)
    - Georgia Outdoor Advertising Association Sales Conference, 1973 (Box AD6 - Letter Size)
    - Industry Relations Committee, 1970-1973, 2 folders (Box AD6 - Letter Size)
    - Industry Relations Meeting, 1972 Feb., Dec., 2 folders (Box AD6 - Letter Size)
    - Legislative Committee Meeting, 1973 June (Box AD6 - Letter Size)
    - Major Media Program, 1973 June (Box AD6 - Letter Size)
    - Marketing Committee Meeting, 1972 Nov. (Box AD6 - Letter Size)
    - Marketing Committee Meeting, 1973 June (Box AD7 - Letter Size)
    - Naegele Meeting [working copies], 1973 Sept. (Box AD7 - Letter Size)
    - Notre Dame Committee Meeting, 1972 Jan., May, Sept., Nov.; 1973 Mar., 5 folders (Box AD7 - Letter Size)
    - NYU Advertising Seminar, 1973 Dec. (Box AD7 - Letter Size)
    - OAAA Committee Lists, 1971 (Box AD7 - Letter Size)
    - OAAA Committee Lists [letters to individual committee members], 1972 (Box AD7 - Letter Size)
    - Out-of-Home Media Committee, 1973 Oct. (Box AD7 - Letter Size)
    - Plans Board Meeting, 1972 Jan., Mar., May; 1973 Jan., Mar., 5 folders (Box AD7 - Letter Size)
    - Plant Development Committee Meeting, 1972 Feb., May; 1973 Mar., 3 folders (Box AD7 - Letter Size)
    - Plant Development Committee Meeting, 1973 June (Box AD8 - Letter Size)
    - Rollins Meeting, 1973 Sept. (Box AD8 - Letter Size)
    - Safety Committee, 1972 Feb. (Box AD8 - Letter Size)
    - Safety Committee Meeting, 1972 Nov.; 1973 June, 2 folders (Box AD8 - Letter Size)
    - S.C. Johnson & Sons, 1973-1974 (Box AD8 - Letter Size)
    - Urban Planning Meeting, 1973 June (Box AD8 - Letter Size)
  - Cawl, Frank- Convention Files - General
    - 66th National Convention, 1967, 2 folders (Box AD8 - Letter Size)
    - Correspondence- Hotel/General, 1973-1974, 2 folders (Box AD8 - Letter Size)
  - Cawl, Frank - Convention Files- Houston
    - Convention Contracts, 1975 (Box AD8 - Letter Size)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box AD8 - Letter Size)
    - Football Game, 1975 (Box AD8 - Letter Size)
    - Hyatt Regency information, 1974-1975 (Box AD8 - Letter Size)
    - Hyatt Regency Special Instructions, 1975 (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
    - Ladies Luncheon and NASA Tour, 1975 (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
    - Special File, undated (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
    - Sunday General Session, 1975 (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
    - Supplier File, 1975 (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
  - Cawl, Frank - Convention Files - New Orleans
    - Arrangements, 1963 (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
    - Convention Program, 1973 (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
    - Cost Estimates, 1973 (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
    - Day-by-Day Functions, 1973 (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
    - Fairmont Roosevelt Meeting, 1973 Sept. (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
    - Head Tables/ VIP Lists- Daily/ Miscellaneous, 1973 (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
    - Ladies Tours and Creole Cooking Demos, 1973 (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous Materials, 1973 (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
    - NOAB Pre-luncheon Cocktail Functions, 1973 (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
    - Notes and Other Information, 1973 (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
    - Savannah Meeting ( Jacl Strong), 1973 Oct. (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
  - Cawl, Frank - Convention Files - Notre Dame
    - Post Chairman Luncheon, 1973 (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
  - Cawl, Frank- Convention Files- Phoenix
    - Hotel Correspondence, 1974 (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
    - Ladies Tours, 1974 (Box AD9 - Letter Size)
    - Limo Service, VIP, 1974 (Box AD10 - Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous Convention Materials, 1974, 2 folders (Box AD10 - Letter Size)
    - Registration, 1974, 2 folders (Box AD10 - Letter Size)
    - Suppliers, 1974 (Box AD10 - Letter Size)
  - Collections- Fairleigh Dickenson
    - Bibliography on the Control of Roadside Development, 1955 (Box AD10 - Letter Size)
    - Biographical Material- Outdoor Companies, 1946-1948 (Box AD10 - Letter Size)
    - Inventory- OAAA Advertising News, undated (Box AD10 - Letter Size)
    - Inventory- Traffic Audit Bureau, 1974 and undated (Box AD10 - Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box AD10 - Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box AD10 - Letter Size)
    - Publications, 1985-1996 (Box AD10 - Letter Size)
    - Special Collections- Forms, 1978 and undated (Box AD10 - Letter Size)
    - Subject Headings, 1965-1970 (Box AD10 - Letter Size)
  - Collections- Other
    - American Advertising Museum, 1987-1988 (Box AD10 - Letter Size)
    - Billboards- Haiku, undated (Box AD10 - Letter Size)
    - Billboards- University of Bridgeport, 1991 (Box AD10 - Letter Size)
    - Duke- Publicity, 1996-1999 (Box AD11 - Letter Size)
    - Friend- R. C. Maxwell Company, 1991-1998 (Box AD11 - Letter Size)
    - History of Advertising Trust, 1986 and undated (Box AD11 - Letter Size)
    - Scott, Howard Collection, 1992 (Box AD11 - Letter Size)
    - National Museum of Natural History, 1986 (Box AD11 - Letter Size)
    - Paver, John Collection, 1993-1997 (Box AD11 - Letter Size)
    - Seidl Jr., Henry, 1987 (Box AD11 - Letter Size)
    - Smithsonian Exhibit, 1995 (Box AD11 - Letter Size)
  - Directories
    - Directors and Elected Officers, 1930-1931 (Box AD11 - Letter Size)
    - Membership Directory, 1940-1946 (Box AD11 - Letter Size)
    - Officers, 1920-1923, 1926-1929, 1974-1980, 4 folders (Box AD11 - Letter Size)
    - Official Directories, 1931-1947, 4 folders (Box AD11 - Letter Size)
  - Exhibitions
    - History of the Poster, 1975 (Box AD11 - Letter Size)
    - Image of America, 1975-1976 (Box AD11 - Letter Size)
    - Whitney, 1936-1987 (Box AD11 - Letter Size)
  - Ghaster, Karl (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - B- Miscellaneous, 1964-1965 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - Birbeck, Charles Reports, 1963 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - Building Officials Conference of America (BOCA), Membership materials, 1949 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - Bulletin Color Charts (Association Standards), 1962-1964 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - C- Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
      [correspondence; manufacturer flyer; 1964 Media Study by Louis Cheskin Associates]
    - The Chips are Down! 1965 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - Construction- Wood, 1949 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - D- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - E- Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - Expense Accounts, 1962-1965 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - F- Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - Farmers and Merchants Bank ( Tulsa, Okla.), Annual report, 1963 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - Foster and Kleiser, 1962-1964 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
      [Correspondence; slide script; article reprint]
    - G- Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - H- Miscellaneous, 1964-1965 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - Holmberg, Lawrence O., 1961-1964 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - I- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - K- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - L- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - Lord, Bissell, & Brook, 1965 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - M- Miscellaneous, 1950-1964 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1950-1962 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
      [Correspondence interspersed with other documents, including a list of Books on Outdoor Advertising, 1927-1932; lists of articles on Outdoor Advertising, 1927-1932; correspondence Re: proposed new statistical service, 1958; operating markets and poster companies; statistical records, etc., 1958; Magazine Digest- contains article by Sidney Katz- Hilda Fox's Battle of the Billboards,1947; booklet- Outdoor Advertising: A Channel of Communications; Description of Industry, 1948; Reader's Digest- article by Thomas C. Desmond- The Coming Billboard Battle,1946; by American Mercury- A Lobby that is a Blot on the Landscape,1947; Cooperative Program for Voluntary Roadside Improvement by OAAA, 1949; Organized Outdoor Advertising: It Genesis, Development, and Place in American Life by Ralph Patch, 1935]
    - National Production Authority, 1951 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
      [regulations, procedures, etc.]
    - O- Miscellaneous, 1951-1965 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - OAAA Washington Office, 1963-1965 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
      [ Fred G. Hussey; Billboard Bonus Act]
    - Ogilvy, David, 1963 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
      [of Ogilvy, Benson & Mather, Inc.; quotes from speeches of 64th annual convention; references to his book- Confessions of an Advertising Man; Today Show]
    - Operation Standards Committee, 1961-1965 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
      [correspondence; journal reprints; specifications of the 24-sheet poster; Loewy panel drawings; Outdoor Advertising News- Mar. issue]
    - P- Miscellaneous, 1964-1965 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - Pacific Outdoor Advertising Company, 1963-1965 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
      [correspondence; interim report]
    - Personal, 1963-1965 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - Public Relations Committee, 1965 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - R- Miscellaneous, 1964-1965 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - Regional Selling Companies, 1962 (Box AD12 - Letter Size)
    - Regional Selling Organizations, 1962 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - Research and Information Committee, 1964-1965 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
      [reports; ground rules; clippings]
    - S- Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
      [ Phillip Tocker file- correspondence; Survival program; sign code; slides (created pocket)]
    - Southern Building Code Congress, 1965 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
      [includes Outdoor Advertising Structures- Engineering Design Manual; NESA Recommended Sign Ordinance; Model Sign Ordinance for Municipalities; Uniform Sign codes, 1958 ed.; Signs and Outdoor Display Structures, 1949]
    - Speakers Bureau, 1963 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - Stoner, Thomas H., 1963-1965 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - T- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - TAB Program Advisory Committee, 1964 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - There is a Future... if..., 1964 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
      [KLG-Rockford, Ill., OAAA (speech by Karl Ghaster)]
    - U- Miscellaneous, 1964-1965 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - US Chamber of Commerce, 1963-1965 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
      [correspondence; Outdoor Poster Panel and Bulletin Advertising: An Economic Report prepared by OAAA, 1957]
    - V- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - W- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - Washington Committee, 1963-1965 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
      [appointment to Washington Committee, Cotton Amendment; C.B. Burkhart trip to DC]
    - Wilbur Smith and Associates, 1962-1965 [ Phillip Tocker file] (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
  - Hathaway, Odell
    - Badge Holder Correspondence, 1959 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, 1934-1959 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1965 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - Correspondence with John M. Paver, 1958-1959 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - Legislation- Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - Obituary, 1966 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - Officers Meeting, 1959 July (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - Photographs, undated (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
      [Photocopies in folder. Original photographic images have been removed and placed in the Photographs and Negatives Series]
    - Swearing in (With Fred C. Beseler), 1959-1960 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
  - Holan, Walter
    - Billing Correspondence, 1966 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - Board of Directors and Officers Meetings, 1961-1962 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - Brand Names, 1966 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - Budget Correspondence, 1965 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - Compensation, 1966 (Box AD13 - Letter Size)
    - Dues and Budget, 1954-1955 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - GFWC- OAAA Art Competition, 1964-1966 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - Ghaster, Karl, 1961-1962 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - Highway Use and Safety Fund, 1965 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - Insurance Correspondence- Charles B. Burkhart, 1961-1962, 2 folders (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - Legislative List, 1966 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - Media- Atlantic Monthly, 1966 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - Meeting Schedules, 1962 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - Membership and Montana, 1931-1965 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965-1966 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - National Convention Data, 1961-1962 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - Officers Meetings, 1965-1966 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - Programs and Budget, 1966 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - Programs and Budget, 1967 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - Proposed 1969 Convention, 1965 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - Rate and Market Service, 1966 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - Research, 1966 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - Storms and Floods, 1927-1951 (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
    - TAB Audits, 1965 and undated (Box AD14 - Letter Size)
  - Holan, Walter - Associations (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
    - Ad Council, 1964-1966 (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
    - Advertising Federation of America, 1966 (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
    - Advertising Research Foundation, 1961 (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
    - ARF Board of Directors Meeting, 1963 Feb. (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
    - Association of National Advertisers (ANA), 1961-1962 (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
    - Institute of Outdoor Advertising Appointments, 1965 (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
    - Institute of Traffic Engineers, 1960-1961 (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
    - National Outdoor Advertising Bureau (NOAB), 1960-1961, 2 folders (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
    - Notre Dame Foundation, 1961 (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
    - Outdoor Advertising Inc. (OAI), 1962 (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
    - Outdoor Advertising Inc. and Association- Staff Meetings, 1961 (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
    - Outdoor Communications Information Centers, 1965-1966 (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
    - Poster Advertising Association of Canada, 1962 (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
    - Regional Outdoor Advertising Associations, 1962 (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
    - Traffic Audit Bureau (TAB), 1966 (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
  - Holan, Walter - Committees
    - Advertising- US Council, 1961-1962 (Folder 1 of 2) (Box AD15 - Letter Size)
    - Advertising- US Council, 1961-1962 (Folder 2 of 2) (Box AD16 - Letter Size)
    - Agency Advertisers Relations, 1960-1961 (Box AD16 - Letter Size)
    - Audience Measurement Standards, 1965 (Box AD16 - Letter Size)
    - Chairman's Advisory, 1962-1966 (Box AD16 - Letter Size)
    - Chairman's Advisory- Appointments, 1965 (Box AD16 - Letter Size)
    - Chairman's Advisory- Industrial Outdoor Displays, 1965 (Box AD16 - Letter Size)
    - Chairman's Advisory- Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box AD16 - Letter Size)
    - Department of Commerce, 1960-1961 (Box AD16 - Letter Size)
    - Dues Review, 1965 (Box AD16 - Letter Size)
    - Industry Relations, 1965-1966 (Box AD16 - Letter Size)
    - Institute Association Coordinating, 1965 (Box AD16 - Letter Size)
    - Membership Policy, 1964-1966 (Box AD16 - Letter Size)
    - Operation Standards, 1965-1967 (Box AD16 - Letter Size)
    - Public Policy Sub-committee, 1961-1962 (Box AD16 - Letter Size)
    - Public Relations, 1961-1962 (Box AD16 - Letter Size)
    - Public Relations- Chairman Appointment, 1965 (Box AD16 - Letter Size)